

FACHRUL ROZI



Job intention: Flutter Dev.

About Me



Hi, I am Fachrul Rozi, right now I am 28 years old. I have jobs experiences for 5+ years as software developer. Right now, I excited to learn new thing, that is mobile development using flutter.

Contact me







Skills

Backend

Experience using .NET and Laravel as framework, use SQL Server and Postgree as DB, integrate to API such as Microsoft API and client API, Deploy using gitlab CI/CD, Experience use azure kubernetes system, etc.

Frontend

Experience using Next JS, Antd, etc.

Mobile

Now excited to develop mobile using flutter. Use GetX and Provider as state management. Integrate firebase services such as analytic, remote config, authentication using google sign in, one signal, etc.

Education

()

Ahmad Dahlan University, 2015-2020

I took Bachelor Degree of Informatic Engineering in Ahmad Dahlan University, Yogyakarta, 2015-2020.

As student, I have several experiences, like:

- Student organization
- Practicum assistant
- Took part-time job
- Got gold medal in International Competition in malaysia.

Experiences



PT. Suitmedia Kreasi Indonesia

I join as .NET Developer in this company started from july 2021 until now. As software house company, I build system those requested by client. We work with style Work From Anywhere.

PT. Sentra Vidya Utama

I joined as Fullstack Web Developer in this company (located in surabaya) started from march 2020 until june 2021. Here, I built a product using Lumen (Laravel micro framework) and Next JS.

PT. Titipbeliin Global International

I joined as Backend Developer Part Time in this company (located in yogyakarta) started from august 2018 until january 2019. Here, I build a product using Django (Python web framework).